[

    {
        "question": "Tömegmérték 1.",
        "answers": [ "1 tonna", "2000 g", "20 dkg", "100 dkg"],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "1000 kg", "2 kg", "200 g", "1000 g" ],
        "answerLanguage": "quiet",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "1 tonna 10 kg= ?",
        "answers": [ "1010 kg", "110 kg","10100 g", "10100 dkg",  "10010 kg", "1000 kg","1000 kg 100 dkg" ],
        "correctAnswer": "1010 kg",
        "answerLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 40

    },
    {
        "question": "1010 dkg = ? g",
        "answers": ["10100"],
        "correctAnswer": "10100",
        "answerLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "10 dkg + 1000 g = ? g",
        "answers": [ "1100"],
        "correctAnswer": "1010",
        "answerLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "Prefixumok",
        "answers": [ "kilo", "deka", "hektó", "deci", "centi"],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "*1000", "*10", "*100", ":10", ":100" ],
        "answerLanguage": "quiet",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Prefixumok 2",
        "answers": [ "kilo", "deka", "mili", "deci", "centi"],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "*1000", "*10", ":1000", ":10", ":100" ],
        "answerLanguage": "quiet",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "Térfogat 1 ",
        "answers": [ "10 hl", "100 ml", "1000 ml", "10 l"],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "1000 l", "10 cl", "10 dl", "100 dl" ],
        "answerLanguage": "quiet",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 50
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Térfogat 2 " ,
        "answers": [ "10 ml", "10 cl", "10 dl", "100 l"],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "1 cl", "1 dl", "1 l", "1 hl" ],
        "answerLanguage": "quiet",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 50
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Tömeg 2",
        "answers": [ "10 g", "100 dkg", "1000 dkg", "1000 kg"],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "1 dkg", "1 kg", "10 kg", "1 t" ],
        "answerLanguage": "quiet",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 50
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Hossz 1",
        "answers": [ "10 mm", "10 cm", "110 cm", "1010 mm", "1000 mm", "1000 m"],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "1 cm", "1 dm", "1 m 1 dm", "1 m 1 cm", "1 m", "1 km" ],
        "answerLanguage": "quiet",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 50
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Hossz 2",
        "answers": [ "1000 cm", "100 cm", "22 cm + 80 mm", "30 dm", "30 mm", "500 m + 5000 dm"],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "10 m", "1 m", "3 dm", "3 m", "3 cm" , "1 km"],
        "answerLanguage": "quiet",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 60
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Hossz 3",
        "answers": [ "10 mm", "10 cm", "10 dm", "1000 m", "100 dm", "500 dm + 500 dm"],
        "correctAnswer": "pair",
        "answerPairs": [ "1 cm", "1 dm", "1 m", "1 km", "10 m" , "100 m"],
        "answerLanguage": "quiet",
        "pairLanguage": "quiet",
        "timeLimit": 60
    }
]